see you
next
time.
So you're saying, you want me
to kill that thing right now?
This adorable living creature?
If we want to survive,
there's no other choice.
Why then you do it, preferably
somewhere I can't see!
Well, it's also an experiment.
No way!
I'm so sorry, little bunny.
I won't be eating meat today.
Oh!
Was that your first time then?
Eating your first kill is
something really special, you know.
Would you like to try it raw?
Someone says they can't eat
meat and you recommend it raw.
What is wrong with you?
Who is this guy?
He seems so shady.
Are you sure about him?
I see you haven't made
the best impression.
I hope you'll put up with me
until we reach the royal capital.
After all, my cart is broken
and my croco-dog ran away,
so now my only means of
transportation is walking all alone.
Nice job.
Since you broke it, we
can't exactly argue. Sorry.
Since my charm doesn't work on
him, I guess it's fine, but...
I'm Tachibana.
I'm Jinguji.
And I'm called Chen.
Both of you have such unusual names.
Where do you two come from anyway?
We can't disclose our personal info considering
how friendly you were with that elf.
I have to wonder if you
might be from the south.
Oh, I totally forgot
about the village head.
You think it's okay to leave her behind?
A woman who'd take our lives
at the first opportunity.
We couldn't bring her.
This squid is delicious.
But the god of your forest
was pretty darn good too.
Yeah. Well. Whose?
fault was that?
Why is it that only my luck increases?
Your physical stats may not improve
at all.
I think I have a rough understanding
of how we level up here.
After beating the first monster, I was
the only one to gain experience points.
But even though the premier helped kill
the squid, your level
increased too, right?
Yeah, now that you mention it.
It's very likely that
Close contact is the key.
That's my guess.
Close contact?
Wait a minute, is that the reason
you made me kill that rabbit earlier?
Why didn't you say so?
You would have objected even if I had.
Hey, I finished making dinner!
Oh, man!
It's so good!
Sorry, Mr.
Bunny, you're too yummy!
I mean, this guy's always
killing stuff so he can eat.
That's pretty amazing.
Jinkoji's hands are really big,
or is it that mine are small?
Hey, thanks for the meal.
Okay, party time.
Um, why are you following me? Hmm?
You could get abducted if I don't, right?
We're in the apartment, though.
And that blithe disregard
brought about the last incident.
I've decided I won't
let down my guard again.
By which you mean you're
going to wait there?
Yes.
Get out!
I can't do this with you here!
So this is your love nest, then? Nope.
I'm a freeloader and nothing more.
But forget that.
Since we're alone now, there's
something I want to ask you.
I want to know why you're following us.
What are your intentions?
Who are you, really?
If he were a townsperson, he would have
specific skills relating to his trade.
Instead, he has assassination
techniques, of all things.
Doesn't bode well.
Maybe while Tachibana is out of the way.
I thought I told you my
intentions earlier, didn't I?
I would appreciate it if you
would allow me to accompany you.
It isn't bloodlust, but what is it I feel?
Is tachibana his target this
must look like a good opportunity
to a slave trader but he
hasn't mentioned it i knew he
was no ordinary man please wait
listen if i had meant to harm
you at all i would have just
put something into the food i
made you
earlier and as it
happens that's just what i did
but only a little something
blast it so tell me how are you
feeling right now your body must
have started to heat up right
poison or some kind of drug taking
our ability to move and then
i gave tachibana a lecture
now look what i've done
my head's foggy i can't think straight
but i can still move which means
Now i demand that you tell
me your true objectives?
Why are you crying?
Splendid.
Your body is just as I'd imagined!
And so?
Shall we begin this now?
That's better
My, you're strong, aren't you?
Uh, whatcha doing?
Don't come closer, Tachibana!
He drugged us.
Now I'm having trouble moving.
It's likely he's after you. Run!
But I can't just leave you here.
After you've escaped,
I'll figure something out.
No way!
If we get separated, we may
never see each other again.
Worry about that after you
get to safety, you idiot!
Desperation. Sweet.
Sorry, Jinguuji.
If I didn't look like this, we
could have stayed together longer.
It's been this way since we got here.
All because I'm so freaking cute.
And that only causes trouble for you.
Tachibana.
Oh.
I don't actually think you're that cute.
To be honest, Tachibana, I'm not really
attracted to you in the slightest.
You don't suit my tastes at all.
I promise I'm not targeting you,
and I've never once thought of
selling you as a slave, so please,
don't even worry.
I'm sorry, have you seen me?
What's with you?
You are a slave trader, right?
Have your eyes rotted out or what?
I think it's your disposition
that's rotten, isn't it?
Don't get lured in!
You have to hurry up and run!
Look, my cuteness happens to be
my entire identity right now.
If that's gone, what else is there?
You just said your cuteness only
caused trouble, and now this?
Since Jinguji can't fight, I'm the only
one who can do anything about this.
You don't seem affected by
me for some reason, but...
I guess it's time for me
to pull out the big gun!
No, not you!
What is your deal?
So you seek to entice me with
that soft, squishy body of yours?
How strange.
It just makes hatred rise
up in me. What'd you say?
I'm gonna show you how
good softness can be! Stop!
If I see something like that when
I'm already unwell, I'll die!
Getting charmed on top of all this!
The cuteness! I can't!
This calls for muscle! A man!
I'll just look at a man
and call him right down!
Looks like your partner got distracted.
He can't maintain interest, I guess.
I feel sorry for you, Tachibana.
But as you can see, Jinguji has
chosen my body over yours. Huh? Huh?
If you think about it,
doesn't it mean that in this moment
I'm more attractive than you are?
Ugh!
Normally I'd be able to say it wasn't
true, but we're talking about Jinguji here!
It's totally possible
you'd choose a male body!
Is that really what you think?
Fine, make a choice, Jinguji!
In your opinion, which
one of us do you want?
You know it's me!
Stop, my brain!
It hurts!
Don't you run away!
Which of us is cuter is a simple question!
Do you really expect me to answer that?
No matter what I say, I'm
choosing a man! A man! A man!
Wait, Tachibana, are you a man?
What is it?
Still a pass.
You're super rude, you know that?
Why are you so squishy?
That body is a crime, you know, seriously.
I agree that it's a crime.
But because of its cuteness, not
its softness, you total weirdo.
Your vanity's on the extreme side, too.
These are the facts, man.
Both of you, please.
Enough already.
Jinguji!
It appears the man has
finally reached his limit.
Don't worry about me. Go. Run!
You're right.
This guy keeps provoking me
and I keep taking the bait
but if he's not interested
in me then What does he want
wait if he's not into me
idiot you're the one who needs
to run Jinguji what I'm
He's not the one Shen wants!
He's after...
Tachibana!
Now then, shall we begin?
No, Shen, stop!
Don't you know you have to get consent
before you do things like that?
What?
Tatsubana, what's happening to me?
Is this torture?
No.
He's giving you a massage.
Really?
The truth is my family has knowledge of
secret pressure points found on the body.
We have secret pressure points?
I guess you could say that I just couldn't
turn away from this level of fatigue.
And if I hadn't been this forceful,
Jinguji probably wouldn't have
let me treat him, would he?
Wow, these muscles are amazing.
Well, Jinguji, buddy, you need a nap?
Shut up.
I'm doing great.
Be careful, you're not
a young man anymore.
The effects of the drug are
stronger the more fatigued you are,
too, so you really had no chance.
It was enough to knock you down.
Please be more self-aware.
Okay, so I've got to ask, did
you give me that drug too?
No, I actually gave
you a laxative instead.
No wonder everything...
well, never mind.
Oh.
Now I'm forbidden to come
within a ten meter radius.
I wonder, how was it that my
true identity was exposed?
Wait, no, it wasn't.
Perhaps he has a sixth sense.
Ah, well, this is certainly
out of the ordinary.
What the...
This is...
Isn't this...
kind of a spoiler?
Are you feeling better now?
Impossibly good.
I guess that means Shen's
got some magic hands, huh?
Listen to me.
From now on if we feel even a little bit
tired let's make sure to take a break!
Tired huh I've Never even
seen this guy catch a cold I
guess it shows how much of
a burden I'm putting on him
At the very least I need to be
able to protect myself I can see it
So that's the royal capital
they've got security
it's because there was a war not long ago
You scared me I told
you 10 meters I thought
you might have some
trouble what do you mean
We can't get inside I don't know of course
I'd be able to guide
you in without a problem
But in return I'd like to show
you around the capital and such
Welcome to the royal capital
Ishurnah look at that the
houses are made of stone so
I can guide You anywhere you
like are there any temples
well let's see the temple of
the goddess of love and
Beauty is right over there why
temple if we can find the
prophecy of the goddess we
might be able To find out a
little regarding the demon lord
cool welcome to the temple
of the goddess of love And
beauty she's so pretty how can
this be she's so respectable
clean tidy polite not a single
issue With her deportment
but this is a temple for
the worship of that crappy
goddess I had an image in My
head of some kind of sleazy
pool party but now you have a
truly powerful imagination oh
oh my are You might you
possibly be hoping to join our
faith she smells so good I can
tell with just one look You
are perfectly suited to being
a servant of our beloved
goddess please you must follow
me this way Is this okay?
For now, but we need to get inside.
There's someone else accompanying me.
Go on, don't trouble yourself over me.
This place is gorgeous.
Yes.
You see, our goddess rules
over love and beauty.
Because of that, the temple
must always be kept beautiful.
And the same goes for us.
We're under obligation as her believers.
First, you must change
into the garb of our order.
Garb, nice, I like the sound of that!
Miss, is there some mistake? Pardon?
This isn't clothing so much as underwear.
Our order's garb.
Like bits of string.
But it's...
You must understand,
that's our official dress.
Only those wearing it are permitted
to enter our place of worship.
I don't...
Please do call for me once you've changed.
I I don't know I don't know
if I can go through with this?
Tachibana you remember our
objective in coming here together?
Info that's right.
No you can't be just steal your nerves I
already have you're
kidding you know all kinds
of stuff is Gonna pop
out of this thing right
are
you done
Tachibana
I'm coming out okay?
What do you mean I'm
wearing it over my suit?
Of course why aren't you
wearing Any clothes are you
being serious you tricked me
now I see what you're doing!
Well,
I hope it was worth
humiliating your only friend
to see me in this glorified
piece of dental floss!
Don't make me out to be the bad guy.
The priestess was wearing
clothes, wasn't she?
Now that you mention it...
Have you finished changing them?
Oh, it suits you very well.
And the gentleman...
I'm still a little reluctant
to show so much skin.
Are you wearing it under your clothes?
Well, as you're observing
today, that should be fine.
Really?
That's fine?
Then I'd appreciate having
something to drape over myself.
In that case, take my robe.
If you think it'll do.
Showing that much skin to someone you've
just met is wrong though, isn't it?
I understand.
I was that surprised when
I first saw it as well.
Quite alright.
I'm convinced one day that
feeling will turn to joy.
Oh, is this okay?
Now, let us go.
It is a sacred space, so
please, no carelessness.
This is our place of worship!
Well, what do you think?
Isn't it the most splendidly
holy site you ever saw?
I always say it's as though the
deities have come to play in the water.
Tachibana, tell me something.
Would you mind if I destroy this building?
Hold it, Tiger.
It's actually just like
you imagined, right?
A pool of revelers enjoying themselves.
It's like it's saying that
my thoughts are on the same
level as that goddess which
infuriates me to no end.
I'm gonna make it like it never existed.
But it's burned into my brain forever.
Well then, let's bring you
into our faith. The faith?
But we only meant to observe today.
Don't worry.
Please just leave everything to me.
You're quite exceptional.
In this world, you could
reach the highest heights.
Miss, I don't. I'm confused.
Please take off your clothes.
But you said earlier I don't need to.
If you try it once, it
will be addictive. No!
Do it!
Take it off!
Let it go! Let it go!
I feel like something
important's been stolen from me.
The first thing that you must do
is make the most of what you have.
You must show even more
of your lovely skin.
What's this?
Why is that on your body?
No, how could this be? What?
Is something wrong with me?
The mark of our gracious
goddess is there on your body?
Oh, uh, yeah.
What wickedness is this?
That isn't something
you should do as a joke!
Hey, exactly what happens to a person
if they have this on their body?
After a proper judgment is done,
there'll be a whipping at best!
And worse, she'll be
sent to a prison island!
There were some words in
there that I did not like.
With such a criminal here,
the very heir will be tainted!
Hurry up and throw her out!
Hands off!
Listen up, believers!
We didn't want this stupid
seal any more than you do!
Trust me, we had no choice!
Stupid seal?
Yes, the crappy goddess's seal!
Of course we'd refuse something like that!
Crappy goddess?
The moment I was handed these swim briefs,
I should have knocked
this temple to the ground!
You weren't even wearing them?!
Why would I do that?!
Everyone, take up your weapons. Yeah!
They shall experience deep regrets
along with our goddess' love in spades!
So now their hate's gone
from me to Jinguuji?
You know, the more people you take
off, the shorter your life's gonna be.
It's more tiring trying
to be considerate of you.
Besides, this is the kind of
development I actually like. Is it now?
What the heck is that?
Impressive magic, right?
That magic binding is meant especially
for the conversion of heathens,
and it won't come off
until you declare your
love for our goddess with an honest heart!
Wait, what?
It's like that thing was
made with Jinguji in mind!
Doesn't this world do anything
to protect freedom of religion?
As I thought, the religions of
this medieval world are worthless.
Until you learn to show some
respect for our holy goddess,
we will continue with your correction!
They're out for our blood!
Nope, no time for that.
Or maybe you're out for theirs.
Ow! My chains! What happened?
They simply weren't strong
enough to be chains.
It can't be done!
I won't allow this to continue any longer!
Oh, goddess in your
exultancy, master of love!
Rhesus, no!
Go ahead!
Fire at me if you dare!
Well, at least you're having fun.
Listen, we did not come here
to spill blood unnecessarily.
All we want is to inspect the prophecy.
The prophecy?
Why would a heathen want that?
I can give you the answer.
These honored people are heroes who
have been summoned here by the goddess.
Hold on, aren't you?
Hear me well, believers.
Interfering with them
is strictly forbidden.
Listen and heed this royal command.
We are doing ourNINGs who will save you
Let's go
Thank you
so
much for watching.
Let's do it!
Do it!
Put it up!
Two more final truth!
Love like that.
Love isn't that. How
like that? and don't you?
It's fantastic!
And you can't act like that.
You can act like that.
But you can't act like that.
Even when you do her.
Just your chance.
You have to do it.
You can act like that.
If you don't want to do it.
Whatever is it, you can act like that.
You can act like that.
I'm not too far.
You don't want to act like that.
Lathers!
We shall not turn our backs on the
teachings of the goddess of love and beauty!
We will bear a body!
That crappy goddess!
I knew it!
She teaches nothing worthwhile!
You!
You have appeared once more!